bidselect.com 2016-12-28

# Privacy Policy - BidSelect

**BidSource Technologies®  
Privacy Policy  
Revised March 1, 2012**

BidSource Technologies® has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate Our firm commitment to the privacy of Our visitors and customers. The following discloses Our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Website: www.bidselect.com.

### A Special Notice About Children

Children (under the age of 18) are not eligible to use Our Site unsupervised and We ask that children do not submit any personal information to Us. If You are under the age of 18, You may only use this Site in conjunction with and under the supervision of Your parents or guardians.

### General

This website (the "Site") is operated by BidSource Technologies®, LLC ("BidSource Technologies," "We," "Our," or "Us"). When visiting the Site, We may ask You to provide information that personally identifies You and/or the employer You work for (collectively, You and Your employer are herein after referred to as "You" or "Your"), for purposes of interacting with the Site; You may also provide confidential information regarding You, Your business, or the business of Your employer (collectively, Your personal information and confidential business information will be referred to as "Private Information").

Although BidSource Technologies® is not a "financial institution" that is governed by the Privacy of Consumer Financial Information Rule of the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act, BidSource Technologies® is committed to respecting the privacy rights of guests and users of the Site. BidSource Technologies® has, therefore, developed this Privacy Policy to protect Your Private Information.

### Collection and Use of Private Information

If You choose to provide information to Us through Our online registration, You may provide Us with Private Information, including Your name, address, postal address and telephone number, Your email address, a password, and other identifying information (such as Your mother's maiden name, city of birth, pet name, etc.). If You choose to use Our Offer Management System (OMS) or purchase a product from Us, We will collect additional Private Information, including Your billing postal address, shipping postal address, and credit card number and expiration date in order to properly process Your purchase. We may also ask You for Private Information when You ask for information, subscribe to a BidSource Technologies® service or publication, or download information.

Your Private Information enables Us to provide You with the information You have requested, provide You with information regarding the status of Your assets and transactions, fulfill Your purchases, and provide You with information regarding future products and services that may suit Your particular interests. We also use Your Private Information to help identify You in the event You lose Your password and to help You quickly find information on the Site.

If You believe that any of your Private Information is incorrect, or has been changed since Your registration at the Site, please send an email message to [support@bidselect.com](mailto:support@bidselect.com) explaining the correction or change and provide any relevant confirmation or reference number.

### Cookies

Our Site uses cookie technology to improve the quality of Your experience. A cookie is a small file that contains information sent by a website that is saved on Your hard disk by Your computer's browser. Cookies store information that a website may need to personalize Your experience and to gather website statistical data. Anytime that You visit Our Site to browse or to read or download information like Our press releases, We collect and store the name of the domain and host from which You access the Internet (for example, msn.com, aol.com, etc.); the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer You are Using; the browser software You use and Your operating system; the date and time You access Our Site; and the Internet address of the website from which You linked directly to Our Site. We use this information to measure the number of visitors to areas of Our Site, and to help Us make Our Site more useful and interesting to Our visitors. We use information from cookies in the aggregate to analyze for trends and statistics, and then discard it - We do not track individuals, only instances of entry onto the Site.

We also use "cookies" on Our Site to enable You to save Your bidselect.com ID information and search parameters.

Most consumers do not know that "cookies" are being placed on their computers when they visit Websites. If You want to know when this happens, or to prevent it from happening, You can set Your browser to warn You when a Website attempts to place a "cookie" on Your computer.

### Do We Share Your Information?

We will share Your Private Information with Our partners and with third-party independent contractors for purposes of: (1) performing functions on behalf of BidSource Technologies®, such as companies that process credit card transactions; (2) providing You with product offers via email and/or postal mail; and (3) for tracking information generated through BidSource Technologies®' Site. Our partners and third-party independent contractors are contractually obligated not to use or share Your Private Information for unauthorized purposes.

BidSource Technologies® may also disclose your Private Information to comply with a court order, subpoena, search warrant or other legal process; to comply with legal, regulatory or administrative requirements of any governmental authorities; to protect and defend BidSource Technologies®, its subsidiaries and affiliates, and all of their officers, directors, employees, attorneys, agents, contractors, and partners, in connection with any legal action, claim or dispute; to enforce the terms of use of Our Site; to prevent imminent physical harm; and in the event that We find that Your actions on Our Site violate any laws, Our terms of use, or any of Our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

We reserve the right to transfer Your Private Information to a third party in the event of a transfer of all or substantially all of BidSource Technologies®' assets, provided that the third party agrees to adhere to the terms of this privacy policy.

### Opt Out

You may opt out of having Your Private Information shared for purposes of receiving: (1) research surveys or product offers from BidSource Technologies via email and/or postal mail and (2) offers from third parties, by simply selecting the appropriate opt-out box(es) available in Your BidSelect profile at any time.

BidSelect will not use your Personal Information for uses prohibited by the provisions of the Telemarketing and Consumer Fraud and Abuse Prevention Act, the Telephone Consumer Protection Act, or the Controlling Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act of 2003, or the rules adopted pursuant thereto by the Federal Communications Commission or the Federal Trade Commission.

### Third-Party Hosting

BidSource Technologies® contracts with a third party to maintain and host the Site. Therefore, any information You submit, including Private Information, shall be placed and stored on a computer server maintained by this third-party host. The third party has implemented technology and security features and strict policy guidelines to safeguard the privacy of Your Private Information from unauthorized access or improper use.

### Site Technologies

BidSource Technologies® does not provide the technologies used to build its Site, and therefore, neither recommends nor endorses the same. Any information regarding identified technologies, their capabilities, limitations, applications, etc., should be sought directly from their manufacturers. BidSource Technologies® hereby disclaims any rights to trademarks, service marks, trade names, logos, copyrights, patents, domain names or other intellectual property interests of third parties.

### Links to Other Materials

This Site contains links to other sites. These links are an accommodation to the respective third-party site owners and for Your convenience. Sites linked to and from this Site are not necessarily under the control of BidSource Technologies® and BidSource Technologies® shall have no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the content or privacy practices of any such linked sites or any link or linking program at any time.

### Security

This Site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under Our control. All credit card information utilizes state-of-the-art Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology and is SET compliant.

### Effective Date and Changes

This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 1, 2012. BidSource Technologies® reserves the right to modify the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time and in its sole discretion, by posting a change notice on this page. Your continued use of the Site following Our posting of a change notice will constitute binding acceptance of those changes.
